patni.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy | iGATE

Your privacy is very important to iGATE Corporation and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (collectively, the “Company”).

This Privacy Statement applies to websites and services of the Company that collect data and display or link to these terms. This Privacy Statement does not apply to those websites or services that have their own Privacy Statement. Additionally, it does not apply to instances where the Company merely processes data on behalf of clients for their benefit, such as when the company provides data storage services.

With respect to personal information collected by the company from the European Union and Switzerland, the Company

abides by the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S. Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of such information (the "Safe Harbor Principles"). For more information about the Safe Harbor Principles or to access the companies certification statement, go to <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>.

 **COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
** The Company receives personal data in several ways. Individuals may choose to voluntarily share their personal data with the Company. For example, you may provide your name, address and other personal information to register for a subscription or a service, so that we can later contact you regarding an inquiry, to process an order, to be considered for employment or to do business with us. 

The Company may also collect information relating to your use of our web sites through the use of various technologies including “cookies” and “web beacons” which allow us to determine, for example, your IP address, browser type, access time and/or viewed pages within our website. A “cookie” is a piece of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as a tag that identifies your computer. Cookies can measure web site usage, allow for ease of navigation for the user, personalize a known visitor’s experience to a web site by being associated with profile information or user preferences. You can set your browser in most instances to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not. You can also generally set your browser to turn off cookies. A “web beacon” allows a web site to collect or transfer information such as whether or not a link has been accessed and what pages within our website have been visited. 

From time to time, we may also collect information that pertains to you indirectly through other sources, such as list vendors or customers. When we do so, we ask the vendors to confirm that the information was legally acquired, that we have the right to use it and our permitted uses.

 **USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
** The Company collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its websites and services (including personalizing the same for you); to provide the products and services ordered by you; to respond to communications received from you; and to implement the purpose for which you provided the personal information including fulfilling requests, processing transactions, evaluating candidates for employment and, in the case of employees and contractors, supporting its workforce and business operations. 

In addition, the Company may use personal data to send you product surveys, newsletters or promotional mailings regarding the Company’s products and services, and may share your information with our business partners so that they may send you information about their products and services; provided, you may ‘opt out’ of receiving such surveys, newsletters or promotional materials by following the steps described in the applicable survey, newsletter or promotional materials.Certain online transactions may involve you calling us or us calling you. They may also involve online chats. Please be aware that it is 

the Company’s general practice to monitor and in some cases record such interactions for staff training or quality assurance purposes or to retain evidence of a particular transaction or interaction. 

Certain social computing tools made available by the Company enable online sharing and collaboration among members who have registered to use them (e.g., forums, wikis, blogs and other social media platforms). Registration information that is not automatically made available to other participants as part of your profile will be subject to and protected in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Any other content you post, such as pictures, information, opinions, or any other type of personal information that you make available to other participants on these social platforms, is not subject to this Privacy Statement. Rather, such content is subject to the Terms of Use of those platforms. Note, the content you post on any such social computing platforms may be made broadly available to others inside and outside of the Company.

 **SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS  
** Except as described in this Privacy Statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of the Company without your consent. You should note that the Company is a global organization with business processes, management structures and technical systems that cross borders. As such, we may share information about you within our corporate group of companies and transfer it to countries in the world where we do business in connection with the uses identified above and in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Our Privacy Statement and our practices are designed to provide a globally consistent level of protection for personal information. 

The Company occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. Moreover, they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose than for delivering the service to the Company in accordance with the Company’s instructions and policies. 

We may disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of the Company or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of the services; or (c) protect the personal safety of the Company’s employees, customers or the public. We may also disclose personal information as part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets; provided, it is the Company’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.

 **INFORMATION SECURITY AND ACCURACY  
** The Company is committed to protecting the security of your personal information and, therefore, implements reasonable physical, administrative and technical safeguards to help us protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure. For example, we store personal information on computer systems with limited access, and encrypt certain sensitive personal information such as credit card information when we transmit such information over the Internet. Moreover, we also require that our suppliers implement reasonable means to protect such information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure.

 **LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES  
** The Company may provide you with links to non-Company web sites. Your use of these links and applications is subject to the third parties’ privacy policies, and not this Privacy Statement. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other web sites.

 **PRIVACY QUESTIONS AND ACCESS  
** If you have a question about this Privacy Statement or the Company's handling of your information, you can contact us at:

iGATE Corporation  
Attention: Privacy Office/Legal Department  
6528 Kaiser Drive  
Fremont, CA 94555 

In certain cases, you may have the ability to view or edit your personal information online. In the event your information is not accessible online, and you wish to obtain a copy of particular information you provided to the Company, or if you become aware the information is incorrect and you would like us to correct it, contact us.

If you have any complaints regarding our compliance with the Safe Harbor you should first contact us (as provided above). If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe online by [clicking here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=), fax to 415-520-3420, or mail to TRUSTe Safe Harbor Compliance Dept., [click for mailing address](http://www.truste.com/about_TRUSTe/contact_us). If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the Company. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution process, click [here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=) or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above.

 **NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES  
** If there is any material change in the way we use, collect or disclose personal information, and updated Privacy Statement will be posted prior to our implementation of any such changes. If we are going to use your personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you either as indicated above, by directly sending you a notification or both, at our option, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we can use your personal information in such a way.

Last Updated: January 9, 2012
